CHRIS ALLEN MADRIAGA

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER



Contact

Address:

Mariwasa St. Pipindan, Binangonan, Rizal

Phone:

0997 681 5214

Email:

madriagachrisallen21@gmail.com

Portfolio:

https://allenmadriaga.netlify.app

Technical Skills

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript/jQuery

Bootstrap

Sass

Git

PHP

MySQL

WordPress

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe XD

Shopify

Summary

Focused Front-End Developer with 1+ year of experience on developing responsive dynamic websites with willingness to learn and master front end frameworks.

Skill Highlights

- Teamwork
- Good Communication Skills
- Problem Solver

Time Management

Experience

Front End Web Developer Intern – April 2019 – July 2019 Front End Web Developer – May 2020 – Present Mindblow Internet Ideas Inc, Mandaluyong

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Convert PSD designs to Responsive WordPress Themes
- Perform direct website updates
- Work with senior developer to manage complex design projects.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- Handle multiple projects on fast paced work environment
- Assist senior developers for minimal revisions on projects
- Managed to finish assigned task on deadline
- Create custom sections and modify Shopify Themes
- Create User Manuals for clients
- Website deployment on cPanel hosting

Education

Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering - 2020 University of Rizal System – Morong Campus

Certifications/Awards

Necklace Awardee | 2018 - 2019 Ring Awardee | 2019 - 2020 TESDA Computer Systems Servicing NCII Passer Speaker – Front End Web Development Fundamentals Workshop